[
  {
    "number": 1,
    "question": "What are the closures?",
    "answer 1": "Both Function objects and Scope where function's variables are resolved",
    "answer 2": "Scope where function's variables are resolved",
    "answer 3": "Function objects",
    "answer 4": "Function return value",
    "rightAnswer": "Function objects"
  },
  {
    "number": 2,
    "question": "var obj =newF();  then  (obj.constructor === F) ",
    "answer 1": "false",
    "answer 2": "1",
    "answer 3": "0",
    "answer 4": "true",
    "rightAnswer": "true"
  },
  {
    "number": 3,
    "question": "what the output?  +true;  !'Lydia';",
    "answer 1": "1 and false",
    "answer 2": "false and Nan",
    "answer 3": "false and false",
    "answer 4": "none of the above",
    "rightAnswer": "1 and false"
  },
  {
    "number": 4,
    "question": "The 'function' and ' var' are known as:",
    "answer 1": "Keywords",
    "answer 2": "Data types",
    "answer 3": "Prototypes",
    "answer 4": "Declaration statements",
    "rightAnswer": "Declaration statements"
  },
  {
    "number": 5,
    "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax to select the p siblings of a div element?",
    "answer 1": "p",
    "answer 2": "div + p",
    "answer 3": "div p",
    "answer 4": "div ~ p",
    "rightAnswer": "div ~ p"
  },
  {
    "number": 6,
    "question": "what is Shallow Copy ?",
    "answer 1": "Shallow copy stores the references of objects to the original memory address.",
    "answer 2": "Shallow copy makes a new and separate copy of an entire object with its unique memory address.",
    "answer 3": "Shallow copy is comparatively slower.",
    "answer 4": "Shallow copy does not reflect changes made to the new/copied object in the original object",
    "rightAnswer": "Shallow copy stores the references of objects to the original memory address."
  },
  {
    "number": 7,
    "question": "console.log('I want pizza'[0]);",
    "answer 1": "'I'",
    "answer 2": "'''",
    "answer 3": "SyntaxError",
    "answer 4": "undefined",
    "rightAnswer": "'I'"
  },
  {
    "number": 8,
    "question": "The CSS property used to specify the transparency of an element is ",
    "answer 1": "opacity",
    "answer 2": "filter",
    "answer 3": "visibility",
    "answer 4": "overlay",
    "rightAnswer": "opacity"
  },
  {
    "number": 9,
    "question": "The correct sequence of HTML tags for starting a webpage is",
    "answer 1": "Head, Title, HTML, body",
    "answer 2": "HTML, Body, Title, Head",
    "answer 3": "HTML, Head, Body, Title",
    "answer 4": "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
    "rightAnswer": "HTML, Head, Title, Body"
  },
  {
    "number": 10,
    "question": "The tags in HTML are -",
    "answer 1": "case-sensitive",
    "answer 2": "in upper case",
    "answer 3": "not case sensitive",
    "answer 4": "in lowercase",
    "rightAnswer": "not case sensitive"
  }
]
